teampromote.com 2014-02-10

# Privacy Policy

#### Privacy Policy

TeamPromote takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. The federal government and technology industry have developed practical tips to help you guard against Internet fraud, secure your computer and protect your personal information.

#### INFORMATION AND COLLECTION OF USE

TeamPromote collects personal information when you register with TeamPromote, when you visit TeamPromote pages. TeamPromote may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. When you register we ask for information such as your name and email address. When you register with TeamPromote and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. TeamPromote automatically receives and records information from your computer and browser, including your IP address, TeamPromote cookie information, software and hardware attributes, and the page you request. TeamPromote uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, and conduct research. You may set up a profile on TeamPromote.

#### INFORMATION SHARING

TeamPromote does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or when we respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. If TeamPromote becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

#### COOKIES

TeamPromote may set and access TeamPromote cookies on your computer. TeamPromote uses these cookies in connection with TeamPromote products and services.

#### NON-PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION

This is information that is commonly made available by web browsers and servers, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. TeamPromote uses this information to understand how visitors use our website.

#### CONTENTS OF ITEMS

The contents of any item that you post directly to the Site, including any text, images, photos, videos and audio, are stored and maintained on our servers in order to publish these items and provide the Service. Your submitted content will be associated with your account.

#### CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

#### THIRD PARTY SITES

This Policy only applies to the TeamPromote website and services. We do not exercise control over the sites that our service links to. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. We encourage you to read such privacy policies of any third-party sites you visit. It is the sole responsibility of such third parties to adhere to any applicable restrictions on the disclosure of your personally-identifying information, and TeamPromote shall not be liable for wrongful use or disclosure of your personally-identifying information by any third party.

#### DATA INTEGRITY

TeamPromote processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Policy. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.

#### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

TeamPromote may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your TeamPromote account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.
